Pride Center of the Capital Region; Records apap361
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Pride Center of the Capital Region Records2011 February 3 - 2017 April 7
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Pride Center of the Capital Region
apap361
28.33 cubic ft. 136 captures
This collection contains four decades of records documenting the day-to-day activities of the Pride Center of the Capital Region.
Collection X
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Biographical History
Founded in 1970 and based in Albany, New York, the Pride Center of the Capital Region promotes the well-being of all lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and queer-identified people and those affected by discrimination based on gender identity and expression. Its programs, both at the Center as well as held throughout the region, meet the health and human service needs of the LGBTQ community as well as educate and advocate for those needs in the broader Capital Region. As the oldest continuously-operating LGBTQ community center in the country, the Pride Center has worked to build a welcoming and empowering community for all people.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of photographs, correspondence, clippings, publications, subject files, and event materials, including records from the annual Capital Pride celebration. The records of the Capital District Gay and Lesbian Community Council includes primarly publications, correspondence, news clippings, and publicity materials. The publications include CommUNITY (1974-2002), Speak Out (1974-1978), Northeast Alive, and Capital District Alive among others. The inventory provided here covers only the publications in this collection. Additional records created by the CDGLCC are also available in the Department of Special Collections and Archives, but have not yet been inventoried.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find. The newsletters are arranged alphabetically.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives. 2016
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. While it is likely that portions of the collection may be viewed, access must be managed by an archivist.
Web Archives; Wages -- New York (State); Pride Center of the Capital Region
- Pride Center of the Capital Region Website, 2011 February 3 - 2017 April 7; 1; 136 captures
  URL
  https://www.capitalpridecenter.org/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: Pride Center of the Capital Region
  created_date: 2016-08-25T19:14:00Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:39:07Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 February 3
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 June 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 June 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 June 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 July 15
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 August 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 August 16
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region | Be proud. Live pride., 2011 September 2
  - Capital Pride Center, 2011 November 2
  - Capital Pride Center, 2011 November 11
  - Capital Pride Center, 2011 December 21
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 January 21
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 February 9
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 February 22
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 March 13
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 April 11
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 5
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 6
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 7
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 9
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 10
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 May 31
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 July 1
  - Buy Viagra No Prescription - Buy Viagra Online Cheap, 2012 July 22
    Scope and Contents
    Meta tag for description: Buy Viagra Online Pharmacy! Best Quality and EXTRA LOW PRICES! Order viagra online without prescription. Buy generic viagra overnight shipping
    Meta tag for keywords: buy viagra, viagra online, generic viagra, cheap viagra, viagra online without prescription, buy viagra online, generic viagra online, viagra no prescription, buy generic viagra, order viagra, order viagra online, cheap viagra online, viagra without prescription, purchase viagra, viagra online pharmacy
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 September 2
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 September 5
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 October 5
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 October 21
  - Capital Pride Center, 2012 November 5
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 January 25
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 March 2
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 April 5
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 May 2
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 May 27
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 June 6
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 July 8
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 July 29
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 August 12
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 August 19
  - Capital Pride Center, 2013 September 13
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 February 27
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 March 8
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 April 21
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 June 27
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 July 4
  - Capital Pride Center, 2014 July 30
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2014 November 3
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2014 December 19
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 February 5
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 February 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 March 17
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 March 21
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 April 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 April 23
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 May 24
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 June 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 July 3
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 July 9
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 July 15
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 August 17
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 September 6
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 September 10
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 October 12
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 November 12
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 December 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2015 December 15
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 January 9
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 January 22
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 February 17
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 March 4
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 March 17
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 March 19
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 March 20
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 April 22
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 May 4
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 May 6
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 May 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 May 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 May 28
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 June 6
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 June 20
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 June 22
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 June 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 June 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 8
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 11
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 12
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 14
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 19
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 21
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 July 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 2
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 8
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 9
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 16
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 23
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
    crawl: 232508
    This item had no crawl rules.
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-08-25T19:20:44Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-25T19:20:44Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-28T19:50:53Z
    end_date: 2016-08-28T19:36:13Z
    elapsed_ms: 260114881
    Crawl Types
    type: TEST_SAVED
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: True
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 259200
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 241065
    novel_count: 62389
    duplicate_count: 1396
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 177280
    downloaded_count: 63785
    download_failures: 2
    warc_revisit_count: 1395
    warc_url_count: 63778
    total_data_in_kbs: 3391265
    duplicate_bytes: 51645407
    warc_compressed_bytes: 182402841
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.25
    kb_rate: 13.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 25
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 28
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 August 30
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 6
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 6
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 9
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 13
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 20
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 24
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 27
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 28
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 29
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 September 29
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 3
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 3
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 3
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 4
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
    crawl: 241073
    Crawl Rules
    Limit host facebook.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twimg.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twitter.com to 500 documents
    start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:51Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-07T20:17:51Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-10T21:16:59Z
    end_date: 2016-10-10T20:41:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 260595260
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    test: False
    discovered_count: 242376
    novel_count: 60987
    duplicate_count: 3589
    queued_count: 177800
    downloaded_count: 64576
    warc_revisit_count: 3588
    warc_url_count: 64569
    total_data_in_kbs: 3422578
    duplicate_bytes: 447835716
    warc_compressed_bytes: 811705156
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 11
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 October 26
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
    crawl: 247622
    start_date: 2016-11-07T20:17:54Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-07T20:17:54Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-10T20:34:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-10T20:19:34Z
    elapsed_ms: 259295153
    discovered_count: 239435
    novel_count: 60745
    duplicate_count: 6469
    queued_count: 172221
    downloaded_count: 67214
    warc_revisit_count: 6469
    warc_url_count: 67207
    total_data_in_kbs: 3427608
    duplicate_bytes: 461867411
    warc_compressed_bytes: 794115439
    doc_rate: 0.26
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 12
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2016 November 13
  - 403 Forbidden, 2016 December 7
    crawl: 253244
    start_date: 2016-12-07T20:27:15Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-07T20:27:15Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-07T22:00:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-07T21:43:32Z
    elapsed_ms: 4509172
    status: FINISHED
    discovered_count: 1113
    novel_count: 1068
    duplicate_count: 45
    queued_count: 0
    downloaded_count: 1113
    download_failures: 0
    warc_revisit_count: 44
    warc_url_count: 1106
    total_data_in_kbs: 108315
    duplicate_bytes: 346437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22687529
    kb_rate: 24.0
  - WARC file for 403 Forbidden, 2016 December 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 January 7
    crawl: 258889
    start_date: 2017-01-07T20:17:35Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-07T20:17:35Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-07T20:54:19Z
    end_date: 2017-01-07T20:40:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 1380120
    discovered_count: 1867
    novel_count: 1392
    duplicate_count: 475
    downloaded_count: 1867
    warc_revisit_count: 475
    warc_url_count: 1860
    total_data_in_kbs: 129910
    duplicate_bytes: 29860738
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22061868
    doc_rate: 1.35
    kb_rate: 94.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 January 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 March 7
    crawl: 271771
    start_date: 2017-03-07T20:18:06Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-07T20:18:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-07T21:07:40Z
    end_date: 2017-03-07T20:57:41Z
    elapsed_ms: 2359321
    discovered_count: 1772
    novel_count: 968
    duplicate_count: 802
    queued_count: 2
    downloaded_count: 1770
    download_failures: 1
    warc_revisit_count: 801
    warc_url_count: 1763
    total_data_in_kbs: 127776
    duplicate_bytes: 35834352
    warc_compressed_bytes: 20002966
    doc_rate: 0.75
    kb_rate: 54.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 March 7
  - Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 April 7
    crawl: 289349
    start_date: 2017-04-07T20:18:22Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-07T20:18:22Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-07T20:44:25Z
    end_date: 2017-04-07T20:34:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 937358
    discovered_count: 2013
    novel_count: 1072
    duplicate_count: 941
    downloaded_count: 2013
    warc_revisit_count: 939
    warc_url_count: 2006
    total_data_in_kbs: 137179
    duplicate_bytes: 35965743
    warc_compressed_bytes: 20559031
    doc_rate: 2.15
    kb_rate: 146.0
  - WARC file for Pride Center of the Capital Region, 2017 April 7
- Newsletters, 1972-2002; 5.33 cubic ft.
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amethyst (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amethyst (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Blade (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Carillion (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Center Post (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Connection (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Empty Closet (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Evening Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 5th Freedom (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Gay Christian (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gay Light (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gay Peoples Chronicle (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gay Teacher Association (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gays on the Hill (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - High Gear, Ohios Gay Journal (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Inquiry (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - In Unity, Series (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Its Time (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Knickerboxer News (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Metroland (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Northview (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Oneonta Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Out in the Mountains (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pan (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - People for the American Way News (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Pink Paper (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Pink Paper (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Produce Report (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Q News (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Recorder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sisters United (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Speak Out (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Speak Out (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - TWT (This Week in Texas) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Transgenderist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Triangle (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Upfront (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Yellow Star and the Pink Triangle (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alive (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amethyst (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amethyst (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Blade (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Carillion (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Center Post (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Connection (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Empty Closet (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Evening Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 5th Freedom (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Gay Christian (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gay Light (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gay Peoples Chronicle (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gay Teacher Association (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gays on the Hill (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - High Gear, Ohios Gay Journal (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Inquiry (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - In Unity, Series (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Its Time (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Knickerboxer News (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Metroland (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Northview (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Oneonta Gayzette (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Out in the Mountains (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pan (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - People for the American Way News (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Pink Paper (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Pink Paper (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Produce Report (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Q News (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Recorder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sisters United (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Speak Out (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Speak Out (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - TWT (This Week in Texas) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Transgenderist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Triangle (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Upfront (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Yellow Star and the Pink Triangle (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Community (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Community (Box 4, Folder 22)